Documentation of criterion 3 1 6.
The pronunciation.
Criterion 3 1 6 or rather the
pronunciation criterion consists in making
available a mechanism to identify
specific pronunciations for words whose
meaning in context is ambiguous if
its pronunciation is not known.
The intent of this success criterion is
to help visually impaired people
and people with vision problems
with reading difficulties in
understanding the contents.
In cases whose meaning often depends on
the pronunciation of
words or characters that
have different meanings, each
with its own pronunciation.
This success criterion can help the
people who have difficulty
decoding words or context
but also those who use
programs for reading aloud.
Some examples of this criterion can
be given by reading the name of an
person show the reading of the words
provide an audio file of the pronunciation
include pronunciation
information using a glossary
or a text that includes information about
the pronunciation of characters shared by
several languages but pronounced
differently in each language.
The applications of the criterion are
I'll just show you a few of them today.
The first method I want to show you is
provide the pronunciation
immediately after the word.
This method consists, as the
title suggests, of inserting
immediately after the word is pronounced.
This will result in a second reading
by the voice synthesizers which will
will read the first word incorrectly
and the second word correctly.
The second method I will show you
will be to insert a link inside the
of the word that you connect to an
audio or pronunciation dictionary.
The third method I want to
show you is the glossary.
The objective of this technique is to make
available the definitions of the word
short phrase by providing the definition
in a glossary. A glossary that
is an alphabetical list of
words phrases and abbreviations with their
definitions. Glossaries
are more appropriate
when the words, phrases and
abbreviations used within the
content refer to a specific
discipline or technological area.
A glossary may also provide the
pronunciation of a word or phrase.
Furthermore, this method is closely
linked to criterion 3 1 3 and 3 1 4.
Which the 3 1 4
is that of abbreviations was 3
1 3 is that of unusual words.
The fourth and last method I will show you
is the use of standard diacritical
marks that can be deactivated.
The objective of this
technique is to provide
users a mechanism to activate and
deactivate diacritical marks.
Many languages use signs and signs
diacritics to indicate the pronunciation
of words or to help distinguish them.
Some languages may use signs
diacritics to indicate vowels to
indicate doubling of consonants
indicate the absence of a vowel or
consonant or for other purposes.
Although it is possible to read the texts
without such diacritical
signs the addition of
diacritical signs can improve readability.
Thank you for watching the video.
They left a time lapse of
the latest modifications.